all right okay well gift will give the
scope he's a few minutes to do a given
will give them a few seconds to get in
here today today was a very exciting day
it's very alright so scope is we need
your help what we're about to ask the
band question it's only on band for the
next couple hours so it's only on band
for the next couple hours
you guys know Eddie right where's Eddie
hey scobie's that's Harold alright
here's the question Eddie needs a car
you guys Eddie needs a car and you know
if you were to come hey I can't lie buys
you a car
so can we ban George from asking bad
questions it's Friday you know what you
know what guys in the interest of free
speech and the First Amendment which
also start with F nothing's banned on
Friday
all right nothing's ban on Friday Friday
is literally the one day that isn't
banned a Camry SE hybrid bro we're gonna
come out with a guide you're gonna be
able to report that yourself look Vivian
sit comes to a disco you have a voice
when you periscope that makes it very
obvious let your periscoping yeah yes
you ever meet Logan Paul in real life
he's so much less obnoxious bro I'm not
rapping maverick merch today I'm repping
comma merch this is a long sleeve white
comma shirt hey you want to show the
nerd recruitment flyers oh my god there
we go
kind of works wow this camera needs some
more dynamic range okay
all right so here's the question you
guys we you know what I'm gonna post a
link in the periscope and we'll go off
what we're going off of well you got we
did get talk all those tacos
we had tacos for lunch bros so I'm gonna
post a link on the periscope oh I got a
log in to comment oh this is too hard
login with Twitter
i authorized out oh okay that was easy
all right cool so here's the thing we're
going off of right now which yeah okay
does it have to be Honda or Toyota no it
explicitly is not to be Honda or Toyota
so we can go anywhere out there and get
literally whatever car
what are we looking at right oh we're
just looking at a goal so we're looking
at we're looking at Volkswagen golf's
yeah so this is how the Germans work how
they buy everything separate or you want
a few money you guys know I'm a fan of
the Audi a4 it might just end up being
out ease of already s4 is so cool so
guys know really what car what car
should be buying cars we think we're
thinking Audi's we're thinking I mean
the VW but VW - no guys I okay let me
tell you about the Chevy blocky one let
me tell you about a Chevy voyage of
course I went to the GM dealer and I sat
in I said the Chevy bolt and it didn't
have power seats okay the band question
is when will my car be supported where
we're buying a new car research is
always research guys but we're trying to
go high-end here
no Subaru no no I don't even want to
hear super super whose band even on
Friday Subarus always bad Tesla Tesla
we're banned from buying Tesla's wait a
raptor what's a rat guys what's a raptor
what's a raptor Oh rose ok ok G Wagen Oh
f-150 Raptor see I'm not from I'm not
from I'm from the suburbs you guys we
drive sport activity vehicles Honda
Ridgeline
that's another pickup truck yeah G Wagen
that's kind of what I'm talking about
guys
classic Tesla that's waiting for Amer
we could do a Tesla to be honest the
amount of Excel well that would think at
Volkswagen the amount of acceleration on
a Tesla scares me because if there are
bugs you're going flying about 40k for a
G Wagen what a deal oh you guys know how
I feel about Ford you guys know I'm just
kind of disgusted by Ford Nissan what
Nissan if we bought a Nissan we'd have
to buy an Eddie how do you feel about a
Nissan Rogue well it got a three star on
Car and Driver
what's an Audi s3 yeah it's like a gold
GTI but way cooler okay okay guys
yeah I would consider a Mercedes too and
i8 bro nobody has one of those oh it's
not that we don't trust our own software
it's just that while we're developing I
mean just the idea of like commanding
torque to an electric motor kind of
freaks me out just if we got a Tesla
Model A yeah it's a lateral it's six
longitudinal that's that's like just
really you could just really fly
alright a sport wagon a golf SportWagen
oh no wait what we looking are we
looking at ease
yeah s3 would be cool three
yeah Ford for more widespread support
[Music]
right I don't want to be in that
position we get the artists who do they
have it on whereas three okay there was
an rs4 I don't think they make so many
more guards they don't make ours towards
an orbiter is it our s3 oh yeah howdy
would be good yeah maybe we should just
buy an Audi but bro zero to 60 in 3.9
seconds no no no no no the elop you guys
could do that at your own weight so does
this come with driver assistance package
all these options are so expensive just
watch the price skyrockets okay no but
let's get a luxury car you guys let's
not get a race car yeah expensive
options
even longer oh my god there's a spider
are you should we get it oh yeah Lexus
yeah we're gonna Lexuses are already
gonna be supported pretty soon we're
renting a Lexus RX r8 the Mercedes
interiors are so nice let's see what's a
future vehicle no not a Volvo okay
Volkswagens strong maybe not a toy I
would already have those not a Tesla Oh
get around outside Raptor not a Cadillac
GM's kind of that's kind of feel that
all the American cars
I never they really are right like
Mercedes Mercedes has the nicest
interiors you got it
cars interiors became uncool after 2004
yeah do what you want to get it you want
to get a used Benz did you know that the
Benz is in the e-class yeah we saw this
we saw the Tesla drives or a fire truck
both dumb shit wait what's cloth the
Mercedes doesn't give you the nice
interior even in the e-class by standard
you need to pay for it it's $4,000 for
leather interior
wait we put on let's put on Maybach
Music you never lend a Maybach music oh
we got into Maybach Music to playlist
really shit I ever wrote chillin in my
Maybach well that's me on periscope me
on periscope Maybach music - what's
scrolling here oh so this here
we're gonna make all the Aeons in the
world take a picture at exactly the same
time so we can do stereo like we're
bringing the phase of the camera in sync
with the GPS or Porsche no no one has
Porsches all right all right guys I'm
thinking I'm thinking Audi you think
Audi
yeah I want you so much does an a3
what's this a smaller a far yeah it's
just a smaller sedan or maybe there's a
hatch n2e try they only make the lecture
cash but I mean I don't know maybe we
just find a four but there's more you
know what why don't we rent an a4 let's
see if we like it I think we like Audi
too much to go with the end you gals all
rights copies Volkswagen and now these
are eventually happening don't get your
hopes up too much if you have a Toyota
Lexus or Honda that's up we're gonna
release a guide and an Acura
yes silver car I so cuz it's good oh
yeah yeah yes yesterday was exhausting I
can't tell the scope is what we were
doing but yesterday was exhausting yeah
yeah right all right cool cool thanks
for joining
cama army what is our product we sell
dash cams shop that comment that I I
always rep the merch comma army be a
scope II join the comma army you can
change the world kids get it up like
young buy one of those no one of those
yeah yeah we got it we got him they're
sick you figured out the end of your
surprise I'll be surprised if you
figured out the Edit you're surprised
come on army all right bye-bye